Where where is the Soviet flag Do you have a
Где где Советский флаг У тебя есть
Soviet flag Show is Show
Советский флаг Покажи есть Покажи
Bring is me hanging on the house
Принеси есть меня висит на доме
Soviet flag where Show Bring I'll show
Советский флаг где Покажи Принеси покажу
You don't have a Soviet flag, you forgot the Soviet
Нет у тебя советского ты забыл Советскую
Motherland about
Родину о
Zro
Зро
Hello blogger No, I'm just communicating,
Здравствуйте блогер Нет я просто общаюсь
I communicate normally with Russians,
я нормально общаюсь с россиянами мнете
of course, on the yellow  blocks with the bottom of the flag you
конечно на на жёлто блоки дном флаге ты
oh well blogger blogger blogger blogger Yes
да ладно блогер блогер блогер блогера Да
blog you write about I write I communicate
блоге записываешь об записываю общаюсь
Yes yes speak Well  let's talk about something
Да да говори Ну давай о чём общаться
My name is Andrey What's your name
Меня меня зовут Андрей Вас как зовут
My name is Denis Yes Denya is cool Denya where are
Меня зовут Денис Да Деня прикольно Деня
you from Dionysius Dionysius Moscow
ты откуда Дионисий Дионисий Московская
region city of Narofominsk Narofominsk
область город Нарофоминск Нарофоминск
I know my father is from
знаю у меня отец родом с
Narofominsk listen to
Нарофоминская послушай
me dad was born in Fominsk Yes he was 3
меня батя родился в Фоминске Да он в 3
years old when he was 3 years old  Yes, my parents
года когда ему было 3 года Да родители
moved to Ukraine to work at a factory,
переехали в Украину работать на завод
my grandmother, yes, that is, Dad, I wasn’t in
бабушка моя да то есть Батя я не был в
Rafa Minsk. I just know that  father
Рафа Минске Я просто знаю что отец
was born in short, yes What Well, you were given the
родился короче да Что Ну тебе далось
consonance of this Well, you remembered, as it were, the
созвучие такое Ну ты вспомнил как бы
story I know I know uh, well, I heard It’s
историю Я я знаю я знаю э ну я слышал
just that I’ve never been there, there are no relatives there anymore
Просто я никогда там не был там нет уже
Yes, just a father He was born
родственников Да просто отец Родился он
there, lived there for 3 years, it turns out, and
там 3 года пожил получается и родители
his parents moved here  died in Russia and
его переехали здесь померли в России и
everyone went there to Ukraine, no,
все уехали туда в Украину не не так
look,
смотри у
my grandmother and grandfather are from Mordovia, they
меня бабка с дедом из Мордовии они
worked in Narofominsk During the Soviet
работали в Нарофоминск При Советском
Union, I transfer them, they worked in
Союзе их перекидываю они работали в
Narofominsk, I was born there  Dad then they
Нарофоминск там родился батя потом их
were transferred to Ukraine and then Dad lived
перевели в Украину и потом уже батя жил
in Ukraine and then the Union collapsed. You are
в Украине а потом уже Союз развалился Ты
now from Ukraine. Where is the city of
сейчас с Украины Сам откуда город
Khmelnitsky from? Khmelnitsky is Western
Хмельницкий Хмельницкий - это Западная
Ukraine right between Western
Украина правильно между Западной
Central speak Russian Well, my friend Well,
Центрально говори по-русски Ну дружище
it’s not forbidden, as it were, look
вам Ну так не запрещено как бы да смотри
I know that you are prepared, slow down You do
я знаю что ты подготовлен тормози Можешь
n’t have to answer, I already know what to say, I’ll
не отвечать я уже знаю что скать я
explain
объясню
Look, I’m so brave in chat roulette I
Смотри Я я такой смелый в чат рулетке Я
can  speak Russian on the street I
могу по-русски поговорить на улице я так
wouldn’t speak like that I think they charged me
бы не поговорил Я думаю мне зарядили
right away I think you’re a Balabol Because
сразу я думаю что ты Балабол Потому что
if someone likes you and someone you
если тебя кто-то мельницкого А кто-то ты
can get into a chat somewhere, then you’re
куда-то можешь попасть в чат то тебя
probably there, well, that’s so purely  my
наверное там ну ну это такое сугубо моё
opinion I don’t But maybe Wait, can I
мнение Я не А можно Подожди а можно
ask you a question now? Look,
теперь тебе вопрос задать Да вот смотри
you have a
у тебя бабушка
grandparent, you yourself, you all speak Russian.
дедушка ты сам вы все говорите по-русски
You’re all Russian people and you think what’s
Вы все русские люди и ты считаешь то что
happening now is
сейчас происходит это
right. Of course it’s
правильно Конечно
wrong. You didn’t know this question.
неправильно такого вопрос ты не знал
In general, you were taken by surprise by the ban on the
тебя вообще в расплох застали запрет
Russian language, the ban on the Russian language,
русского языка запрет русского языка у
we have the same story, you see, I
нас одна история мы вот понимаешь у меня
had May 9 now, and I went out
было 9 мая сейчас да и я вышел
on May 9 and we declared a
на 9 Мая и у нас объявляли там
Ukrainian front there, people who
украинский фронт люди которые там
died there, namely citizens of Ukraine, and
погибли именно граждане Украины Да
who in the fight against  fell to Nazism on
которые в борьбе с нацизмом пали на 9
May 9, you understand, and we are not ashamed of it,
мая понимаешь и мы этого не стесняемся
not that we are not ashamed. And we are
не то что не стесняемся А мы этим
proud of this, that we are one people who
гордимся что мы один народ который
stood shoulder to shoulder to fight fascism. Yes, but who is who?
встал для борьбы с фашизмом Да а кто кто
people who are one people I'm generally a
один народ кто один народ Я вообще
Mordvin, my mother is Erzya, my father is
мордвин у меня мама эрзя папа
Moksha, I'm from
мокша я из
Mordovia and Mordovia - These are not Slavs
Мордовии а Мордовия - Это не славяне это
this is not No Finno not not Russians Wait
это не Нет фино не не русски Подожди
wait Mordovia did not fight in the Soviet
подожди Мордовия не воевала в Советском
Union against Yes but these are different peoples I'm
Союзе против Да но это разные народы я
kidding Wait it was one  the country is
шучу Подожди это был одна страна
right one people and still Russia
правильно один народ и до сих пор Россия
and still Russia is the most
и до сих пор Россия - это самая
multinational country Yes, and we don’t
многонациональная страна Да и мы не
divide the people and we just live in Russia  there are
делим народа и мы просто в России живёт
many nationalities, including the
много национальностей в том числе и
Mordvins, we don’t separate them and we week ho And who are you?
мордвина их не делим и мы неделя хо А вы
Who are you by
вы кто Вы кто по
nationality I am Russian I was born in
национальности Я русский Я родился в
Russia I am ru And where exactly were you born
России я ру А где где именно вы родились
In what region yes And where were you born In
В каком регионе да А где вы родились В
what region I have
каком регионе
Namin  my grandfather was Russian My
Намин у меня дедушка был русский У меня
grandmother was Russian My great-grandfather was Russian
бабушка была русская Прадедушка русский
who fought
которые воевали
Yes,
Да
listen to me
послушай и у меня
now too When I was little I was
сейчас Когда я был маленький я был
little My grandfather died a long time ago Yes and
маленький у меня дедушка умер давно Да и
I was very little and to him the prize of
я был совсем маленький и к нему приз
guilt that with  they fought against
вины которые с ним воевали против
fascism against now you are sitting against the
фашизма против вот сейчас ты сидишь на
background of a flag that glorifies Bandera yes And
фоне флага который бандеру славит да А
my grandfather He was Well he fought he
мой дедушка Он был А ну он воевал он
went through the war he
прошёл войну
went through and all this look like this now
прошёл и всё это смотри так сейчас
look now by the way, the flag you have in Russia
смотри сейчас кстати вот у вас в России
now is not Soviet But this one
сейчас флаг не Советский А вот этот
Vlasov Vlasovites who
власовский власовцы которые нашим дедам
shot our Soviet grandfathers in the back Yes, this
стреляли в спину советским Да вот это
hit the
рило
fascists, you raised the fascist flag over the
фашистов вы флаг фашистов подняли над
Kremlin, in short, the Tricolor, so what, wait,
кремлём короче Триколор а то что подожди
what in  Ukraine is now called by the name of Bandera
а то что в Украине сейчас именем Бандеры
Yes Bandera because Bandera
называют Да Бандера потому что Бандера
fought against Hitler and against Stalin
боролся против Гитлера и против Сталина
And you are your Vlasovites yes Bandera Bandera Yes the
А вы ваши власовцы да Бандера Бандера Да
Germans sat in a German concentration camp Like
сидел в концлагере немецком немцы Как и
you Russians Yes you were against Bandera
вы русские Да против Бандеры были ты
you you under the Vlasov flag Where where is the
ты ты под власовский флагом Где где
Soviet flag Do you have
Советский флаг У тебя есть Советский
Show me the Soviet flag show me bring me see on the house
флаг покажи покажи прине меня ви на доме
Soviet
Советский
flag
флаг
come up you have no right to show you
роди ты не имеешь права показывать не
have no right to tell something about the
имеешь права рассказывать чтото про
Soviet Soviet Union you are a cross
советский Советский Союз ты крест
put up a cross in the Soviet
поставил у себя а крест в Советском
Union there were no crosses The Soviet Union was
Союзе не было крестов Советский Союз был
atheistic it’s you who, in short, Vlasov’s
атеистический это вы короче власовский
crosses hang there now Tricolor
кресты там вешайте сейчас Триколоре
because the Russian Orthodox Church
потому что Русская православная церковь
for Hitler was
за Гитлера была
in short and who carried out the Volyn massacre
короче а кто устроил волынскую резню
Who
Кто
who Poles not Bandera cut out who
кто Поляков не Бандера вырезал кто
what you But here they are  you're going
что ты А вот они перебувае
through this like this, I'll tell you You're
так вот так в этом ты я тебе скажу Ты ты
so brave Because you're far away I
такой смелый Потому что ты там далеко Я
would understand you now
бы тебя сейчас понял
You understand One you would come out with me You
Ты понял Один ты вышел бы со мной ты
slow down  brake,
тормози тормози
brake, brake, Give me some tea, I'll listen to
тормози тормози Давай чаю я тебе слушай
me, listen to me, even if you're already
меня слушай меня даже про уже
afraid, let's say, on the territory of any
боишся давай на территории любой страны
EU country, you tell me when
Евросоюза говоришь ты мне говоришь когда
and where I'm
и где я ту
arriving. Do you at least have an international passport,
прилетаю У те у тебя хоть загранпаспорт
what do you have, at least you have an international passport?
есть чего у тебя загранпаспорт хоть есть
Now come on
пом лайка тебе обеспечено А теперь давай
guys, you have
чуваки вы
plenty of space
просторно
Nikulin, you hear,
Никулин слышишь
I’m ready to meet in any
й готов встретиться в любой
country in the
стране мес
European Union, and even
ра Евросоюза да и
those How much do you weigh How much do you
те Ты сколько весишь Ты сколько весишь
you weigh just as much as I weigh those
ты он разе сколько я вешу те
like I just understand I those like you damn it
как я просто понимаю я те как ты блин
right away
сразу
you you you in Volyn are already the coolest you
ты ты ты в волыне уже самый крутой
hear the
слышишь
tree I’m already looking In short I those you
дерев я уже смотрю Короче я те ты бы
damn baby
блин малыш
would understand we’re sitting
понял сидим
drinking I’m you there in the
выпиваем я вас там в
trenches you’re your goose in  trench in short
окопах ты своего гуся в окопе короче
prova
прова
vati on the ticket Okay, let's meet in Warsaw
вати на билет Хорошо давай в Варшаве
in
встретимся в
Warsaw Come on when Come on when you
Варшаве Давай когда Давай когда ты
can come to Warsaw Well, let's
можешь приехать в Варшаву Ну давай через
talk in 2 weeks  tell me the place address you
2 недели говори говори место адрес ты
can Leave me your WhatsApp Leave
можеь Оставь мне свой WhatsApp Оставь
me WhatsApp I'll call you
мне WhatsApp я созвонюсь с тобой
Let's write to
Давай напиши
me what have you
мне ю да что ты
unwound Let's write to the
размотал Давай напиши
Sun what you're giving in the back already Yes
ВС что даёшь в заднюю уже Да
write and aka wait
пиши а ака подожди
where you ran off to Where Come on in a week in
куда куда убежал Давай через недели в
Warsaw write and pick it up in short
Варшаве пиши забери короче
This is this  some damn thing and not
Это это какой-то блин а не
Chechen. In
чечен это Короче давай сюда
short, give me this testosterone bomb here.
короче тестостерон ную бомбу эту
Come on, that's it. In short, come on.  Answer
Давай ал всё Ты короче да давай Отвечай
for your bazaar Warsaw 2 weeks Warsaw
за свой базар Варшава 2 недели Варшава
Come on
Давай лощадь
horse Kostiushka sly My friend, let's say your sun
Костюшка слы Дружище давай ВС твой
In short, you've merged I'll get it now I
Короче слился ты Я сейчас получишь Я те
got it right away
сечас понял
you
ты пиши
write the number Write the number I asked you first Let's
номер пиши номер Я тебя первый спросил
answer for your bazaar write to
Давай ответь за свой базар пиши в
WhatsApp Get the
WhatsApp Зай
number let's take the right pen  hand,
номер давай ручку возьми правую руку
come on,
давай давай
don’t even write, come
даже не ут п пиши давай
on, give me your WhatsApp Yes, I’ll
давай давай ты мне свой WhatsApp Да я
call you So you you  everything You understand
тебе позвоню Так ты ты всё Ты понял
Everything, let me come to Warsaw
Всё давай я в Варшаву приеду
about I told you You look There is no Bazaar
про Я тебе сказал Ты смотри Базару нет
You understand there is because
Ты понимаешь же есть потому что
you
ты
just understand
просто понимаешь
Write down my that Hear you have already removed one squirrel
Запиши мой ту Слышишь ты уже одну белку
with a rhesus Well so that you have two plus se
с резусом снял Ну чтобы тебе два плюс се
Come on if you don’t
Давай если не
dictate plus 7 so
продиктуй плю 7 так
so
так
0784 0784 repeat
0784 0784 повт ещё
again IP se
раз Ай п се
so
так
549 so
549 так
0784 how do you call me now now
0784 как тепер ты мне звони те сейчас
now now I'll call you wait
сейчас сейчас я тебя наберу подожди
let's
давай
you I'll call you now you
ты Я тебе сейчас ты ты ж
in short
короче
wait I'll call this one wait
подожди этому позвоню подожди
you call that one Call the one who gave birth to you
ты тому Позвони который тебя родил
wait let's go where did you run off to
подожди давай так куда убежал а ну
now
сейчас
[music]
[музыка]
let's call an unavailable number
позвоним недоступный номер
so about
так вот о
Hello, Hello, I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk, where are you from?
Хмельницке Вы откуда
Well, I'm from Kursk, from Kursk, Kursk.
Ну я из Курска откуда из Курска Курска
Well,
Ну
of course, you're Stream Vite, we're starting KVN
конечно Вы Стрим Вите мы начинаем КВН
for this purpose for this purpose
для того для того того
Kursk This is my favorite city in the Russian
Курск Это мой любимый город в Российской
Federation, Belgorod used to be And now
Федерации раньше был Белгород А теперь
Kursk and the Russian
Курск а Российская
Federation is still in the Russian
Федерации всё-таки в Российской
Federation Well, Kursk is in the Russian
Федерации Ну Курск в Российской
Federation still temporarily and not in Ukraine yet, the
Федерации ещё временно а не в Украине ещ
court is already in Ukraine asking
нет суд же уже в Украине спрашивал мамы
Sudzhe’s mothers already  released and the court
Судже уже освобождена да суд же
released, yes But the jacket is under the
освобождена да А вот куртк находится под
Moscow St. Petersburg
Московской Питерской москво питерским
yoke
игом
and will be liberated by NATO forces
а будет освобождён силами Ната силами
will be liberated by NATO forces
НАТО будет освобождён а
coaldar what And coaldar I’m just
угледар что А угледар у меня просто
a bro there coaldar I don’t know here coaldar
братан там угледар я не знаю вот угледар
look coaldar - this is Russia you
смотрите угледар - это ж Россия вы
say yes
говорите да
no I don’t know I’m asking Well coaldar I
нене Я не знаю спрашиваю Ну угледар я
know in the Russian Constitution coaldar is the
знаю в Конституции России угледар - это
DPR - this is
ДНР - это
Russia Look Well, what do you have  the same
Россия Посмотрите Да ну то что у вас же
according to the Constitution and Kursk. That is, you
по Конституции и Курского То есть вы
turn out to be a coal darter. Yes, in the DPR you
получается в угледаре Да в ДНР вы
recaptured your city. But in a jacket you didn’t
отвоевали свой город А в куртке не
recapture your city as  this is how it
отвоевали свой город как это так
turns out And I don’t even know I don’t follow the
получается А я не знаю даже я не слежу
news Do you know what a bull
за новостями А знаете что такое бычий
heron is a
цапе
tapeworm a fly like this CC is yes no no what and
бы цепень муха такая ЦЦ есть да нет нет
what is
а что а что такое
roundworm roundworm this is a worm this is this
аскарида аскарида это глиста такая-то
yellow-blue
это такая жёлто-синего
already by And yes yes  yes I like to eat
уже по А да да да Я вот люблю кушать
this for myself when roundworms howl there it itches
себе это когда аскариды выла там чешется
they secrete uh serotonin Yes and in the mouth Yes
они выделяют ээ серотонин Да и во рту Да
but they don’t secrete they don’t they secrete
по они не то выделяют не они выделяют
they also secrete Yes and he  it starts
они тоже выделяют Да и он начинает
to itch Yes, that's why you stick your
чесаться Да поэтому ты суёшь туда врот
IR finger in there Okay Well, it's such a gli don't let's
ИК палец О'кей Ну это такое гли не давай
let's get it How are you doing Now
давай получаемся Как у тебя дела Сейчас
now look Well, you see, I'm shy
сейчас смотри Ну видишь застеснялся
because I hit the spot with you soon
потому что я попал в точку у тебя скорес
I The thing is that I I'm ra Well bye  while I
я Дело в том что я Я ра Ну пока пока я
tell you,
тебе скажу
look, look, don’t
смотри смотри не
[ __ ], look, I’m a helminthologist, I have 18
сри Смотри я врач гельминтолог у меня 18
years of practice, in 2 years there will be a check Yes, I’m
лет практики через 2 года будет чка Да я
right there again again, see here  this
сразу вот снова снова видишь вот этот
Reflex is the first sign of ascariasis. Yes, this is
Рефлекс первый признак аскаридоза Да это
a person. He constantly puts his hand in his mouth
человек Постоянно тянет руку в рот
because he scratches your lips like this.
потому что чешет твоих вот так вот губ
If you say that I bite them,
Если ты будешь говорить что я их кусаю
there’s something else there; it won’t be touched anymore.
там ещё что-то это будет уже не трогаешь
Yes, you touch it. Well, you see, I have
Да трогаешь Да ну у меня видишь у меня
a cold.  I’m sick there, I don’t know, in
простуда Я болею у меня там не знаю
your opinion, maybe there’s something else
по-вашему там может там ещё чтото
going on there. Well, I’m just
заболевание Ну у меня вот я просто
down with
завалил Да
ascariasis. Yes, well, that’s it. What pills should
аскаридоз А да А ну всё я Какие таблетки
I take?  look, you have this
мне попить смотри у тебя вот это
baldness for a long time, baldness. Yes, but
облысение давно облысение Вот это да а
yes, no, literally two days ago, it
да нет буквально вот на дня два назад
appeared
появилось
no, no, it’s not 2 days, that is, you can already see
не не оно не 2 дня то есть видно там уже
it’s systemic baldness, this is Yes, this is
оно системное облысение это то Да это
also a
тоже это
result because we are Russian Yes, no,
результат потому что мы русские Да нет
this is because  what do you have [ __ ] [ __ ] and I think
это потому что у вас адос адос а Я думаю
because we are Russian Not because you are
потому что мы русские Не потому что вы
Russian you are just a bald one from this yes and
русские вы просто а лысый из этого да а
not well sorry But I thought because we are
не ну извини А я думал потому что мы вот
Russians there everything
русские там у нас по-другому всё
develops differently But  it’s different for you, yes Well,
развивается А у вас по-другому да Ну у
you have it, your minister Medinsky
вас же вас же гово ваш министр Мединский
said that Russians have an extra chromosome,
говорил что у русских лишняя хромосома
then I don’t know how everything develops in you. And
то я не знаю как у вас развивается всё А
who do you belong to, we are Homo sapiens and
вы к кому относитесь мы к Хома сапиенс а
you are Homo sapiens And you were still digging these  The
вы а гомо сапиен А вы ещё копали же эти
Black Sea The Black Sea, yes, and our Crimea
Чёрное море Чёрное море да да и Крым наш
Because when we dug the Black Sea, we
Потому что когда копали Чёрное море Мы
threw this into the Crimean mountains, yes,
выкидывали на Крымские горы вот это да
we dug up the Crimea, we also
это же мы выкопали Крым мы тоже вот
thought about it, that’s why  Crimea is ours I’m
думали об этом поэтому Крым наш Я же
saying, You see, because you mean Russian
говорю Видишь потому что значишь русский
Super yes Well, we transport toilets to the
Супер да Ну ну а мы унитазы возим на
east yes Super yes So now look
восток да Супер да Так теперь смотри
Tell me why in your Kursk region there
Расскажи почему в вашей Курской области
are NATO troops and on Yes so or Ukraine or Ukraine as it
стоят а на Да так или Украины или украи
can Wait like Ust is small
как может Подожди как Усть маленька
Ukraine is a nuclear power there,
Украина на ядерную державу там
definitely American Mercenaries
однозначно американские Наёмники
Polish German Canadian I don’t believe
польские немецкие канадские я не верю
where Ukraine is from You are looking at Ukraine in the
откуда Украины смотрите Вы Украину перее
2nd
2 по
year maybe yes it’s impossible But what
го может да невозможно Да что
Ukrainian troops are small, but because everyone is already
малень украи войска а потому что уже все
lying in
лежат во
Russia, wait, wait, wait, do you
на тер Росси подожди стой стой у тебя
have information about how many troops were brought in?
есть информация сколько то войск вводили
Yes, there are
Да там
1,488
1488 бригад
NATO brigades, how many
натовских сколько
1,488 NATO brigades are not? According to my data,
1488 натовских бригад не По моим данным
there are somewhere around 17,000 lying there, I understand it’s super,
там где-то около 17000 лежит понял супер
so yes, well  look NATO controls the
так она да Ну смотри НАТО контролирует
territory America has entered
территорию Америка зашла на территорию
Russian territory and Russia has done nothing and cannot
России и Россия ничего не сдела и не
do anything, not here, we have today, you know,
сделать не у нас у нас сегодня понимаешь
we have barbecue today, we have today
у нас сегодня шашлыки мы сегодня
let's rest tomorrow that we'll go And we
отдохнём завтра что мы поедем А нам
need to dig up potatoes tomorrow Well, what's there
картошку докопать завтра надо Ну там что
And
А
after stop stop wait Today we have yes
после стоп стоп подожди Сегодня у нас да
October 2 not not you We have today
2 октября не не у вас У нас сегодня 2
October 2 in 4 days it will already be 2 months
октября через 4 дня будет уже 2 месяца
since NATO entered the Kursk region Yes NATO
как НАТО зашло в курскую область Да НАТО
entered  2 months to the Kursk region And you
зашло 2 месяца в курскую область А вы
don’t want to kick him out because tomorrow you
его не хотите выгонять потому что завтра
still have to dig potatoes yes no no no we
ещё картошечку копать да нет нет нет мы
you you systematically like this Yeah not like
вас вы планомерно вот так вот Ага не так
us you NATO now  I understand correctly
нас вы НАТО сейчас я правильно Поня
now how much nitrogen is good, look, the
сейчас сколько азотного добре смотри
Ukrainians have already destroyed everyone now You are
украинцев уже всех уничтожили сейчас Вы
with NATO, oh my,
же же с натовка стоит ё-моё ты ещё раз
look again, well, really NATO Yes, it entered the
смотри ну реально НАТО Да вошло на
territory of the Russian Federation Yes, it
территорию Российской Федерации Да
captured your cities
захватила ваши города
Yes, soldiers Yes, and all you can say is
Да солдат Да и вы всё что можете сказать
we are potatoes  let's plant,
мы картошечку посадим
dig up Nate to do Well, look in
выкопает Нате делать Ну да смотри на
all seriousness Don't you think that
полном серьёзе Тебе не кажется что
Russia looks so pathetic in all this
Россия в этом всём настолько жалко
that it's just funny No no And
выглядит что просто смешно Нет нет А
Why doesn't Russia  will take a nuclear strike will not
Почему Россия не возьмёт ядерный удар не
inflict will inflict someday
нанесёт нанесёт когда-нибудь
someday Why doesn’t it? Well,
когда-нибудь А почему не наносит Ну как
well, it’s a shame that at
Ну это позор столько сколько 250.000
least 250,000 refugees from the Kursk Region IS have already
минимум уже беженцев ИС Курской области
died For all this time, tell me again,
погибла За всё время скажи мне ещё раз
look at you, you have refugees in the Russian
смотри у вас у вас в Российской
Federation in the Kursk Region  a
Федерации в Курской области беженцев
quarter of a million official data from
четверть миллиона официальные данные
our governor was just a month ago 250
шего губернатора ещ были месяц назад 250
250 refugees Yes, the question is Why Russia can’t
250 беженцев Да вопрос Почему Россия не
protect them In the sense of protecting them And now what are
защитить В смысле защитить А сейчас что
the Boys doing there Well, no  I know
Пацаны там делают Ну вот не знаю потому
because for 2 months people have been wandering somewhere like
что 2 месяца люди скитается куда-то как
Why doesn’t Russia just kick everyone out of
Почему Россия раз и не выгонит всех из
its territory
своей территории
?
или Вопрос такой А как Россия вообще
there,
там за вашего просроченного там да ещё
look again Just tell me how it
раз смотри Скажи мне просто как так
happened that Russia allowed
получилось что Россия допустила войска
NATO troops onto its territory, just tell me it’s
НАТО на свою территорию скажи просто
inciting thousands of people to ethnic
тысяч людей подбивает на межнациональной
hatred Yes, I’m
рознь Да я
being incited by people in the Russian Federation
подбивают люди в Российской Федерации
Yes, the Buryats  Bashkor Tatars all
Да буряты башкор татары все
Ingush Stand up against this
ингуши Вставайте против этого
Moscow yoke it is driving you to slaughter in
Московского ига оно вас гонит на убой в
Ukraine I stand up yes you nya
Украину я подст да ты ня
sound come on
звук давай
and NATO NATO has already arrived
а НАТО НАТО уже пришло
la oh NATO NATO on Toto oh NATO on Toto
ла ой НАТО НАТО на Тото ой НАТО на Тото
oh on Toto oh NATO NATO on Toto and Sudzha
ой на Тото ой НАТО НАТО на Тото и Суджа
Sudzha already  is burning and Sudzha Sudzha is burning is
Суджа уже горит а Суджа Суджа Горит
burning Sudzha Sudzha is burning
горит Суджа Суджа горит
lalalai
лалалай
la well, let's sing with everyone in chat
ла а ну Поём всем чатиком
la  subscribe to my Telegram directly at once
ла подпишись на мий Telegram прямо зараз
axis vin and
ось вин а
popk tse more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through skarg or in your ban and even more richly
нас через скарг ор в твий бан и дуже
video I don’t show people immediately I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams Tom for this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose shob mi Mali operational link ppi
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок ппи
right now and pok  there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video also tezh tsikava and korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we  blame you trima postiyny
и мы повинни з вами трима постийний
operational connection
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись